{
    "subject": "resource/Agus_Wirahadikusumah",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Indonesian general",
    "human_readable": "Agus Wirahadikusumah's description is an Indonesian general.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9717883467674255,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Agus Wirahadikusumah's role as an Indonesian general?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8657006621360779,
            "question": "When was Agus Wirahadikusumah active as a general?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8057240843772888,
            "question": "What is Agus Wirahadikusumah known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7949097156524658,
            "question": "How is Agus Wirahadikusumah remembered in Indonesian history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.770423948764801,
            "question": "What were the major events during Agus Wirahadikusumah's time as a general?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7378116250038147,
            "question": "What nationality is Agus Wirahadikusumah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7110715508460999,
            "question": "What country is Agus Wirahadikusumah from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.69234299659729,
            "question": "What profession does Agus Wirahadikusumah have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580647230148315,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements associated with Agus Wirahadikusumah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49646028876304626,
            "question": "Is Agus Wirahadikusumah a military leader?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Agus Wirahadikusumah's description is an Indonesian general.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3018_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable achievements associated with Agus Wirahadikusumah?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3018_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Agus Wirahadikusumah have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3018_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Agus Wirahadikusumah from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3018_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3018_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The documents mention Agus Wirahadikusumah as a high-ranking Indonesian military officer and commander of Kostrad, which supports the description that he is an Indonesian general."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Agus Wirahadikusumah was an Indonesian general. He held several high-ranking positions in the Indonesian military, including Commander of Kostrad and Head of the Planning Directorate in the Armed Forces Headquarters of Indonesia. Additionally, he faced political consequences related to his role within the military, such as being dismissed from his post due to anti-corruption activities, which further supports the description of him as a high-ranking general in the Indonesian armed forces."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}